http://www.seatow.com/privacy

Skip to Content
close
profile
Sea Tow
JOIN »
RENEW »
Reviews
Why Sea Tow?
Privacy Policy
Sea Tow is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. This privacy policy covers important aspects of how we respect and protect your privacy, including: Awareness, Information Gathered, Use of Information, Third-party Use, Choice, Accuracy & Access, Security and Enforcement.
Awareness
Sea Tow provides this Privacy Policy to make you aware of our practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and from the bottom of every web page of our sites.
Information Gathered
On our website or mobile app, you can do some or all of the following:  become a member, renew your membership, manage your account, buy a gift membership, subscribe to our newsletter, register for an MMSI number, order products, chat with us, email us and request information. The types of personal information collected at these pages may include your name, address, contact and billing information, transaction and credit card information and information about your boat(s). Additionally, any information you supply due to promotional programs, refer a friend programs or special offers may be collected.
In order to continuously improve our products and services, we may also ask you to provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experience with our products and services, and more detailed contact preferences.
When you access our website or mobile app, we may automatically collect information that is not personally-identifiable including, but not limited to, the type of browser or device and computer operating system you use; the domain name of the website from which you came; the device ID number, the number of visits, average time spent and pages viewed. We may use this information and share it with our worldwide affiliates to measure the use of our websites and mobile app and improve their content.
Use of Information
Sea Tow uses your information to better understand your needs and to provide you with better service. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete transactions, to communicate with you, to update you on services and benefits and to personalize our website and mobile app for you. Credit card numbers are used only for payment processing and are not retained for other purposes.
We may also use your information to periodically contact you for market research or to provide you with marketing information we think would be of particular interest to you. At a minimum, we will always give you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving such direct marketing or market research contact.
Third-party Use
Sea Tow will not sell, rent or lease your personally identifiable information to others. Unless we have your permission or are required by law, we will only share the personal data you provide online with other Sea Tow entities and/or business partners who are acting on our behalf for the uses described above. Such Sea Tow entities and/or business partners are governed by our privacy policies with respect to the use of this data and are bound by appropriate confidentiality agreements.
Choice
Sea Tow will not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without first letting you know and offering you a choice. We will also provide you the opportunity to let us know if you do not wish to receive unsolicited direct marketing materials from us and we will do everything we can to honor such requests.
Your permission is always secured first, should we ever share your information with third parties that are not acting on our behalf and governed by our privacy policy.
Accuracy & Access
Upon request, Sea Tow will provide a summary of any personal information retained by Sea Tow. You may modify, correct, change or update your personal information or cause it to be removed from Sea Tow's database. We try to ensure that any information we collect and maintain is reliable and current.
Individuals who desire additional information on the accuracy of and access to their personally identifiable information should contact Sea Tow’s Compliance Officer at:
Compliance Officer
Sea Tow Services International Inc.
PO Box 1178
Southold, New York,11971 USA
info@seatow.com
Any links to third-party web sites are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave our site or mobile app. Sea Tow has not reviewed all of these third-party sites and does not control and is not responsible for any of these sites, their content or their privacy policy. Thus, Sea Tow does not endorse or make any representations about them, or any information, services, products or other materials found there, or any results that may be obtained from using them.
Security
Sea Tow is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy and to ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online and through our mobile app. For example, we use encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information.
We cannot guarantee the confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted to/from Sea Tow via this site or mobile app, however. For more private communication, you may contact us by telephone at (800) 473-2869.
Any inquiries concerning security should be reported to Sea Tow’s Compliance Officer. Contact information is provided above.
Enforcement
Individuals who wish to file a complaint or who take issue with Sea Tow’s Privacy Policy should direct such communication to Sea Tow’s Compliance Officer at the address above. Sea Tow’s Compliance Officer will explain the process to be followed when filing a complaint.
Sea Tow Services International Inc. is subject to the jurisdiction of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. Should an individual be unable to resolve a complaint by contacting Sea Tow’s Compliance Officer, they may contact the Federal Trade Commission at the following address:
Federal Trade Commission
Attn: Consumer Response center
600 Pennsylvania Avenue NW
Washington, DC 20580
consumerline@ftc.gov
www.ftc.gov
Information Placed Automatically on Your Computer
When you view one of our websites or mobile app, we may store some information on your computer or mobile device in the form of a "cookie" to automatically recognize you the next time you visit. Cookies can help us in many ways, for example, by allowing us to tailor a website to better match your interests or to save your password so that you do not have to re-enter it each time. If you choose not to be recognized, please refer to your Internet browser to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored.
Children
No personal information should be submitted to Sea Tow's websites or mobile app by children without the consent of their parent or guardian. Sea Tow encourages all parents or guardians to instruct their children in the safe and responsible use of their Personal Information while using the Internet. Sea Tow will not knowingly collect or use any Personal Information collected from children for any purpose whatsoever, including disclosure to third parties.
Policy Changes
The foregoing policy is presently in effect. Sea Tow reserves the right to change this policy at any time and we will post such changes. By entering the Sea Tow website  or mobile app you are accepting all terms and conditions outlined in the above Privacy Policy.
Join »
Renew »
GoSEARCH »
Life Jacket Loaner Stations
Contact Us!
Why Sea Tow?
Sea Tow Services International, Inc.
All Rights Reserved.
Search Results
×
